<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/atmawarin/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/atmawarin/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 180 hours tether that binds everything so you can ignore that relentless button nudges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/atmawarin/articles/the-180-hours-tether-that-binds-everything-so-you-can-ignore-that-relentless-button-nudges/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/atmawarin/articles/the-180-hours-tether-that-binds-everything-so-you-can-ignore-that-relentless-button-nudges/</guid>
      <description>You are will and substance.&#xA;Not a puppet string or pawn to be nudged around by every Tom, Dick, or Harry. Nudge. Nudge. Nudge.&#xA;The added wealth, the new doors, the expanding network— everything that you think would make you the king of the hill, well, sometimes they just god darn quicksand. You might mistake that pull for lifeline rope. They fling open doors to new junctions, possibilities, and -urgh– expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Alasan Pindah Dari Wordpress ke Webflow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/atmawarin/articles/6-alasan-pindah-dari-wordpress-ke-webflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/atmawarin/articles/6-alasan-pindah-dari-wordpress-ke-webflow/</guid>
      <description>Merawat medium bernama website pribadi yang bisa dikontrol sendiri, dibuat sendiri, dipublish sendiri, merupakan salah satu hal yang paling cerdik yang pernah saya lakukan. Dari situ saya belajar coding, eksperimen tipografi, dan juga menulis. Punya website pribadi bagi saya sangat manjur untuk mengasah skill, mempertemukan saya dengan orang-orang baik dan juga membuka jendela bagi karir professional saya.&#xA;Untuk platform, saya sudah coba macam-macam. Mulai di 2008 dari platform blogging yang bernama Multiply (sudah punah sepertinya), saya pindah dan mencoba Wordpress, ExpressionEngine, Jekyll, hingga pure no CMS dengan modal Codekit app di Mac, sebelum akhirnya settle kembali di Wordpress.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
